Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Michigan Conference records 1955-1957 IBT0028
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Michigan Conference Records
1955-1957
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
IBT0028
1 Linear Feet
This collection contains yearly reports. The material dates from 1955-1957. These are the yearly reports of the Michigan Conference of Teamsters, a regional governance body in the structure of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters.
Arrangement
Organized into 1 series: Yearly Reports
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains yearly reports. The material dates from 1955-1957. These are the yearly reports of the Michigan Conference of Teamsters, a regional governance body in the structure of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters.
Michigan; Labor; Labor unions; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Conferences
- Yearly Reports, 1955-1957; Series 1; 1 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the yearly reports of the Michigan Conference of Teamsters from 1955-1957 and includes hours, wages, and working conditions of the Michigan Conference of Teamsters.
  - Yearly Report [Part 1 of 2], June 1953; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Yearly Report [Part 2 of 2], June 1953; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Yearly Report [Part 1of 2], June 1955; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Yearly Report [Part 2 of 2], June 1955; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Yearly Report [Part 1 of 2], June 1956; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Yearly Report [Part 2 of 2], June 1956; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Yearly Report [Part 1 of 3], June 1957; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Yearly Report [Part 2 of 3], June 1957; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Yearly Report [Part 3 of 3], June 1957; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Yearly Report [Part 1 of 3], June 1958; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Yearly Report [Part 2 of 3], June 1958; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Yearly Report [Part 3 of 3], June 1958; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)